Hello, Seeno!
We are the research students of STAPLER
I'm Moana Chihama!
I am Mizuki Yasui!
Yes, we are currently 12 members of the STAPLA research students!
Today, I would like to share with you the charms of the 12 of us!
Yay!
Remember me and go home!
I'm not going home!
Watch this! I'm not going home!
Watch it!
Well, first of all, I would like to introduce myself!
First of all, I, Senhama Moana!
First of all, my name is Moana Senhama!
I am 15 years old and a freshman in high school!
My hobbies are watching stage performances, sap and dancing!
My skill is Karate and I am a black belt!
My charm is Moana!
My name is Moana!
I think my name is Moana because it's so unique, or is it unforgettable?
Yes, it's unforgettable.
Have you ever forgotten it?
No, not yet. Not yet.
So, once you hear the name, you will say "Oh, my gosh!
I also told my mother and father that "Moana" means "ocean" in Hawaii.
My mother and father gave me the name Moana because they wanted me to have a broad heart like the ocean,
So, I think Moana is very attractive,
May I introduce myself here?
Please do it!
Then, let's do it!
Please do it with me!
Here we go! Se-no!
Vanda rabbit koala! Vanda rabbit koala! Vanda rabbit moana!
I'm Chiba Moana, a high school freshman who wants to be your legendary ocean!I'm Momoa Chiba, a high school freshman who wants to be your legendary ocean!
So cute!
Okay, I'll go next.
My name is Mizuki Yasui, and I'm a 16-year-old high school sophomore.
I was born on February 26th.
My hobbies are playing music and watching dramas.
My special skills are playing basketball and wiggling my right eyebrow.
May I?
I'll go.
Surreal, isn't it?
What? Like a right nerve twitch?
I'm a wizard.
Oh, I see.
That's why I'm so charming.
I melt people's hearts with my sweet cheeks.
You melt people's hearts?
But Mizuki's always melting my heart.
I've always been melted by Mizuki.
I'm kind of shallow.
I don't know...
What was that?
Did you hear that?
He said it wasn't shallow.
It was shallow.
I don't know.
Like when he's eating.
He makes a face like he's about to explode.
You know...
Blush.
And her cheeks...
They're so soft and fluffy.
What is it that makes your heart melt?
Oh, hey, you know what?
I'll introduce myself after I use this.If you use this, I'll introduce myself.
Can I do it now?
I'd love to.
My charm in life is my cute little cheeks.
I'm going to melt everyone's heart.
I'm Mizuki Mizuki.
It's done!
No, seriously. At live events,
I'm going to give it back to you," the fans responded,
I was like, "What? Like, "Oh, my God!
Like, "You got me.
Everyone is specialized.
It makes me happy, doesn't it?
Mizuki's nickname is Mizuki,
When we talked, she would say, "Mizuki, I want to eat this, too,
And her hand is right here, too.
Can you see that?
You can see the person with a coy smile.
Everyone does this and asks for favors,
Also, when we were filming,
When we were filming, she was always looking up at me,
Their eyes are so bright and shiny,
Here's one for the camera.
Isn't this Azato?
I want some Mizuki ice cream.
Can I have some?
What?
Azato is a lump.
I think it's a girl named Azato, Supply Student #1.
On the contrary, Yasui-san, do you already have blood?
Yes, I do.
What?
No?
No, I don't. But I'm always firm, or not firm enough.No, not anymore, but aren't you always firm, firm?
What?
But I'm kind of good at switching it up.
You know, before the lesson starts, you're all bubbly and bubbly,
But once the lesson starts, you're already sharp as a tack.
You know.
You are, aren't you?
What's that?
I'm babbling.
I don't know what to say.
The atmosphere is different from the lesson.
I wonder.
Is it that different?
That's it. Before the lesson, you're all sparkling.
You're sparkling, and you're talking so animatedly,
I love it when he gets into the lesson and starts to concentrate.
Thank you.
Do you want to have a praise contest?
Yeah, I do.
Oh, really?
Another praise contest today. I'm going to win.
Are you gonna be mad?
What?
But I did it earlier.
I'm sure.
I got it.
Well, this time, I've introduced Ma and Mizuguchi, but from next time, I'd like to introduce the rest of the Sakura research students.
Please watch for the next installment!
Bye bye!
This program is sponsored by Ms. Eri Eri
Yoshitaka-kun 66
Keisuke
Natsu-san
Mr. Guratanglutamic acid
Mr. Iwaki
Mr. Robin Cop
Tomohisa
Mr. Serika
Koga Inu
I'm going to work my magic now!
Shaan!
Now you can be a Stapler student dorico!
Thank you very much!